MAXIMILIEN LAJONY

LEVEL DESIGNER





Portfolio: Video games



06 86 45 64 44



max.lajonypro@gmail.com



agaki.itch.io

EDUCATION

ENJMIN VIDEO GAME MASTER DEGREE

ENJMIN, Gobelins Paris

2021 - 2022

Game Design, Level Design, UX, UI, Producing, Gamification, Programmation, Animation

COMPUTER SCIENCE MASTER DEGREE

CESI NANCY

2015 - 2018

Object programmation (C#, C++), IT Management

SKILLS

DESIGN

- · Level design Document
- 2D top down plan
- 3D gray block prototype level
- POI map
- Gameplay elements intergration
- Photoshop | Substance | Blender

TECH

- Unity
- Unreal Engine 4, 5
- C# C++ Python Dialogs scripting
- Git / Jira bug tracking software

LANGUAGES

• French: Native

• English: Fluent Toeic - 780

PROFILE

Passionate about video games, I decided to make it my job by specializing in **level design**. I created several games and gamified projects but my main project is a 3D adventure puzzle game that received a **publishing proposal**: **Amon**. What I like about **level creation** is bringing places to life, which tell a story while serving the gameplay. I also have a **developer background** which allows me to adapt to technical situations, in particular in **C#**.

EXPERIENCES

LEVEL DESIGNER / GAME DESIGNER / PRODUCER GAMIFICATION PROJECTS (VR / AR / METAVERSE)

REALITY

2021 - 2022

- Game Design (Game loop, Game design documents, Scoring, Puzzles design)
- Level Design (2D/3D grey block, level integration)
- Producer (Meeting leader, Prog team leader, Gantt, Monday.com maintain)

LEVEL DESIGNER - GAME DESIGNER - NARRATIVE DESIGNER PRODUCER - AMON (ADVENTURE / PUZZLE 3D GAME - UNITY)

ENJMIN - Gobelins professionnal project

2022

- Level Design (3D gray block, puzzle creation and implementation, event integration, architecture of environnements and creation)
- Game Design (game loop, abilities and mechanics documentation)
- Narrative Design (script writing, world building, lore)
- Producer (Team leader, Meeting Leader, Gantt, Git & Monday.com maintain)

DEVELOPPER C# / DEVOPS / IT MANAGER

Euro Information Developpement - Credit agricole - EIDA

2015 - 2021

- Developper C# for internal bank software for credit management
- Devops (scripting and server management) for bank
- Project manager in Luxembourg (IT team leader of 4 persons) & Developper fullstack (C#, Angular, SQL, BDD)

GAMEJAMS

2021 - 2023

- Narrative Designer World Builder : Bridge Colossus | Visual novel | 1 week
- Level Designer, UI, VFX / Environnement Artist: Carriage Nightmare | Coop rail shooter | 48 hours